This is the chaotic time of
spontaneous gangs.
In order to scramble for territory...
they are not afraid
to purge each other...
despite the rules.
Butcher...
slaughter...
to survive.
Until the formation of four forces.
These four hold hundreds of juniors
under their command...
creating a balance in the underworld
during the time.
They are known as:
Cuong...
Area: Cho Lon - Weapon: Chopper
Business: Protection, loaning.
Hao...
Area: Float Market - Weapon: Scimitar
Business: Protection, smuggling.
Chan...
Area: Cau Muoi Market - Weapon: Ice saw
Business: Protection, restaurants.
Hung.
Area: Night Market - Weapon: Pig chopper
knife Business: Smuggling, prostitute.
Long!
I'm fine.
Big Brother is in trouble.
Call Hung.
Phong!
Kill him!
What the hell?
Boss!
We gotta run!
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you come here, asshole?
You bastard!
Big Brother! Run!
Dad!
Run for your life!
Run!
Dad!
Are you all right?
Hanh!
Hung?
Get my father out of here first.
Let's go, Big Brother.
Cop!
It's time for you to pay me.
Did you really have to do that?
CARDS ON THE TABLE
What is punch-drunk syndrome?
It's a form of brain injury.
Mild symptoms could include hearing loss...
and vision loss.
The severe condition could lead to…
How about Phong?
He's still in a coma...
but he's out of danger.
Fighting and killing...
whether you win or lose...
bring loss.
Why...
are the choices of people I care...
about never include me?
How did things come to this?
You still have your brothers.
But...
I only have you now.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep our child.
Drugs.
Night Market.
Hac Hung and even Phong.
It was all Chan's plan.
Had I been more thoughtful at that time...
Phong wouldn't have been like this.
Did Dung tell you anything else?
That was all she could hear.
Who is Cop?
Seems like Chan
wants to swallow up Cho Lon.
You should quit after this.
There's one more thing.
Ba's calling.
Tell him to stay there,
don't go back to the city yet.
Long's father is on the way to Saigon.
You guys wait for me at the hospital.
Fighting him!
Fuck!
Dad!
Your father's condition has gotten worse…
he needs emergency surgery.
Dad, it's me, Long…
Please hold on, dad…
Dad!
My goodness…what happened to your face?
I'll explain later.
Dad!
What happened to you?
I'm okay.
Some bastards blocked my way.
Mom!
How…how is my dad, doctor?
Why didn't you focus on studying?
You're always watching those stupid movies!
- I'm not! Dad!
- You learned martial arts for what?
You're never studying!
Go check on him.
As you know...
they played dirty
with Big Brother over and over.
We can't keep standing by to watch.
We must show them who we are.
Lu!
Who released these bastards?
Cho Lon is the fortune that Big Brother...
has built over the past 20 years.
Why are you taking such a reckless gamble?
A traitor like you is not
qualified to say that to me.
Traitor?
There's something...
I have to clarify.
First...
I indeed cooperated with Chan.
Second...
it is true that I met Hien.
But do you know why?
Because he returned my dumb-ass son to me.
Release this one.
And the last thing...
Chan sold drugs inside schools...
I didn't know this.
And that violated
my ultimate forbidden rule.
This wasn't in our contract.
Therefore this war...
I will not participate.
I came here...
to clear his name.
For me, brothers are above all.
You guys will handle your own problem.
And I'll handle my family's problem.
Let's go home.
One party has withdrawn...
the balance is back.
You don't seem happy.
Yeah, I got it.
I guard him...
even more carefully
than babysitting my own child.
Okay.
Long!
Holy moly!
Ouch!
Long!
Are you nuts? What the hell are you doing?
Keep…going…
Have you checked on Phong?
You only do crazy things all the time.
Yes, I have.
Take care of yourself first.
He won't die easily.
That coward Hao is off the table!
Are you guys ready?
Go!
You have a phone call, Long!
Long, your phone's ringing!
Long?
Long!
Holy moly!
You're insane!
I'll give you one last chance.
Leave Cho Lon
to follow me and you will live.
Otherwise...
you will die.
You want me to join you?
Get the fuck off, you son of a bitch.
Go on!
Why do you come here?
Long! Have you lost your mind?
You're gonna kill him!
Stop!
Fine!
You won today.
Cho Lon will…
Will never lose!
Big Brother!
I don't dare accept
those two words from you.
It was such a waste...
of using my flesh to save you...
from being stabbed last time.
Big Brother!
By any standards...
everything I do, I do it for Cho Lon.
I want you to prosper.
I want every brother here
to have more money.
Why are you being so uptight?
Lu!
Gangsters must still
rely on society to survive.
You'll never be able to live long...
with that type of income.
I am sick of you!
Hey, Big Brother!
Don't you hear people say?
A wise man changes his mind, a fool…
Is you, Lu!
Yes!
It's me! So what?
A traitor will always be
a traitor sooner or later.
Long!
Ba!
Take care him!
Hung, where are you going?
Hung!
Can you protect
hundreds of brothers in our gang?
Spit it out!
Holy crap, you'll be doggone!
Damn it, spit it out!
How dare you
touch my best friend's girlfriend?
Brothers for life!
We live and die together!
Cheers!
99 LATERS DAY
Phong, come here and help me!
Okay!
Ut Det! I'm home!
What took you so long?
I bought some offerings
for Hung's 100-day funeral ceremony.
Phong, come give me a hand!
I'm here!
Ut Det!
It's dangerous to walk around
during pregnancy.
Let me carry you!
You silly!
Holy moly…
Long!
Yes?
Can we cook this now?
Ok!
You're insane!
Ba!
Have you ever done this with Ut Det?
I haven't.
I save it for our wedding night.
Be quiet…
or my dad would hear…
Jeez, it's Long! I thought that was my dad.
You scared the hell out of me!
What are you doing in here...
that you're so scared of
your dad finding out?
Sex...
sex movie.
But didn't you tell me...
to come over
to watch Bruce Lee's movies?
You're keeping it.
Yeah…
[THE BIG BOSS - BRUCE LEE]
What happened?
Some bastards came over…
They took all the money.
I don't know who they are.
Is Ut Det okay?
She's fine.
Big Brother?
A Hien?
Big Brother? A Hien?
They were the Night Market.
Here, I give you some.
Thank you.
Chan had escaped.
Hac Hung is planning something.
Don't let Hung's death become meaningless.
I heard it.
Roger that!